mrnumber.com 2010-10-19

# Privacy Policy - Mr. Number

_Last Updated: May 25, 2010_

Mr. Number, Inc. (“ ** _Mr. Number_** ”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of the Mr. Number website located at [http://mrnumber.com](http://mrnumber.com/) (the “ ** _Site_** ”) and any services or software offered by Mr. Number (including but not limited to our Mr. Number Mobile App and our Mr. Number Back Up, Mr. Number Caller ID and Mr. Number Reverse Lookup services) (any and all of the foregoing the “ ** _Mr. Number Service_** ” or “ ** _Mr. Number_** ”). This Privacy Policy applies only to information provided to us by users through Mr. Number.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. 

As used herein, the term “ ** _Non Registered User_** ” means an individual who has (i) submitted his or her Profile Data (as defined below) to Mr. Number so that information can be made available to Members; or (ii) submitted his or her phone number to Mr. Number to request that we block information from appearing in Mr. Number results; and the term “ ** _Member_** ” means a user who has registered with Mr. Number and created an account. Please see our Terms of Service located at <http://mrnumber.com/legal/terms> and our FAQs located at <http://mrnumber.com/help> for more information about how you can manage the data you choose to submit to Mr. Number. 

### Information – What We Collect and How We Use It

**What we collect.**

We collect information from users to provide and improve our Site and the Mr. Number Service and to administer use of Mr. Number by Members and Non Registered Users. This information includes “ ** _Cell Phone Data_** ” which is the data contained on a cell phone which you choose to upload to Mr. Number , including but not limited to your cell phone contacts and your cell phone number; and “ ** _Profile Data_** ” which is the data and any other information that you choose to submit to us as a Member or Non Registered User to display in Mr. Number Caller ID or Mr. Number Reverse Lookup results for your own phone number, including but not limited to your name, phone number, and other contact details. 

In the course of using Mr. Number, some of what we’ll ask you for is considered “Personal Information.” This term refers to personally identifiable information about you that can be used to contact or identify you. Such Personal Information typically includes but is not limited to your name, phone number, email address, credit card or other billing information, and home and business postal addresses. While some Personal Information is required to join Mr. Number, you have the option to provide additional Personal Information in your Mr. Number profile. 

We may also ask for other information, such as your zip code and personal preferences, which is typically considered “Non-Identifying Information” since it can’t be used to identify you on its own. Sometimes Non-Identifying Information can be considered part of your Personal Information if it is combined in such a way that it enables you to be identified (for example, combining your zip code with your street address). 

**How we use it.**

We use your Personal Information (in some cases with your Non-Identifying Information) mainly to provide the Mr. Number Service, and to respond to your inquiries.

We may also use your Personal Information with your Non-Identifying Information and combine it internally with information collected from other Mr. Number Users (as defined below) so as to provide you with a better experience; improve Mr. Number and understand how our services are used; and to serve you specifically, for instance to send you administrative notices or to deliver a product to you according to your individual preferences or restrictions.

Except as set forth in the section below titled “Information Sharing and Disclosure”, we never disclose your Personal Information to anyone without your permission. 

_Technical Data._ When you visit the Site or interact with one of our services, whether as a Member, Non Registered User or a visitor just browsing (any of these, a “ ** _Mr. Number User_** ”), our servers automatically record certain information that your browser transmits so that we may keep track of which of our services you access. We do this in order to ensure that the elements of the Mr. Number Service are available to you and customized for your use. During this process we may also collect your IP address and browser details, as well as store cookies in your browser, all of which help us personalize and improve Mr. Number. While you have the option to stop your browser from accepting Mr. Number cookies at any time, if you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of Mr. Number or all of its functionality. For more information on how to stop accepting cookies, please refer to the help menu for your web browser. 

_Additional Phones._ Mr. Number is for use only with cell phones that you own and control. We may send a security code to your cell phone by text message to confirm that you own any phone you use with Mr. Number. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

_All Mr. Number Users._ Any comments or submissions that you post to our corporate weblog, phone number complaint website, and support forums will be publicly available. Any information you choose to provide in a comment or a submission should reflect how much you want other users to know about you. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and we encourage Mr. Number Users to think carefully about what information about themselves they disclose in their comments or submissions.

_Members._ If a Member has your phone number, we will display the information from your profile to them. If you opt in to our free Caller ID service, Mr. Number will use the information in your address book, in addition to information made available via other third party sources, to provide names for other Members who look up numbers. If you prefer not to allow Mr. Number to use the information in your address book in this manner or you do not have the permission of your contacts as required by the Mr. Number Terms of Service, do not opt in to use the free version of Mr. Number Caller ID. (Merely downloading and registering for Mr. Number does not opt you in to Caller ID. You must activate this feature inside the app.) Mr. Number will not use any information from your address book if you only use Mr. Number Reverse Lookup, a service that requires you to type in numbers one at a time in order to get a result.

_Non Registered Users._ If you have submitted your Profile Data to Mr. Number this information will be shared with Members in accordance with the “user preferences” you set to make your profile visible. 

_Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information._ We combine your Cell Phone Data and Profile Data and the data of many other Mr. Number Users into anonymous sets of “aggregated information.” All Personal Information is stripped out and all cell phone records are replaced with random numbers. We share this aggregated information, Non-Identifying Information, and log data with third parties for analysis so that we can continuously improve Mr. Number. We will not, however, share your Personal Information for these purposes. 

_Service Providers._ We may employ third party service providers to assist us in administering and providing Mr. Number. However, service providers never have access to your Personal Information in non-encrypted form except for information that they need to perform a specific task on our behalf. For example, a company managing our email list will have access to your email address if you receive email from Mr. Number. Such service providers are obligated not to disclose or use the data to which they have access for any other purpose. With your explicit prior permission in each case, we also provide outside technology developers who have registered with Mr. Number access to your Personal Information so that they can deliver products and services that you request, which may be used to enhance your use of Mr. Number.

_Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement._ Mr. Number will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Mr. Number or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

_Business Transfers._ Mr. Number may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information and your Cell Phone Data or Profile Data, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy. 

### Changing or Deleting Your Information

All Members may review or delete their account at any time. To review your account, go to <http://mrnumber.com/login>. To delete your account, go to <http://mrnumber.com/account/cancel>. 

All Non-Registered Users may review, update, correct, delete, or block their Profile Data from Mr. Number at any time by going to <http://mrnumber.com/profile>. (Deleting your Profile Data will not delete the data that may be held by Members in their Cell Phone Data. Deleting your Profile Data means that your name will not appear in Mr. Number results.) 

With respect to any data you have taken steps to delete, Mr. Number backs up data nightly for your protection, so it may take up to 30 days for all trace of your Cell Phone Data or Profile Data to be erased from our systems. 

### Security

Mr. Number is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

### International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to – and maintained on – computers located outside of your state, province, country or other jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your area. If you are located outside the United States and you choose to provide your Personal Information to us, Mr. Number will transfer it to the United States and process it there. By consenting to our Privacy Policy, and submitting information, you agree to that transfer. 

### Links to Other Sites

Our Site contains links to other websites. While we do our best to link to reputable sites, the fact that we link to a website or present an ad is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites and we encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of other websites that you visit. 

### Our Policy Toward Children

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with such information without the parent’s or guardian’s consent, he or she should contact us at privacy@mrnumber.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

### Phishing

Mr. Number is concerned about identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing.” We treat safeguarding your Personal Information as a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited email or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website.

### Contacting Us

And of course, if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@mrnumber.com.
